A Guide to the Alfred E. Cohn papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA132
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1
  - Freeman, William B., 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Fremont-Smith, Frank, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Fry, Varian, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Francis, Thomas Jr., 1943 1947 1953 1955 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Fraser, Francis R., 1943-1945 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Fraser, Francis R., 1946-1951 1953 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Friedenwald, Jonas S., 1941-1942 1945 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Gasser, Herbert S., 1935-1939 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Gasser, H.S. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Galati, Charles, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Galdston, Iago, 1937-1939 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Gebhard, Bruno (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Geiger, Arthur, 1936 1939 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Gilchrist, A. Rae, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Glick, M.B. (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Glueck (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Glueck, Bernard ca, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Galati, Charles, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Gamble, James L., 1951 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Gilbert, Charles K., 1952-1953 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Gerard, Gabrielle, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Garrison, LLoyd K. [re], 1953 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Ginsberg, Harold, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Ginsburg, Sol W., 1947 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Galati, Charles, 1940-1943 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Galdston, Iago, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Gallus, Wilya, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Gamble, James L., 1942-1943 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Gardner, Warner W., 1940 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Gaynor News Co., 1945 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Gebhard, Bruno (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Geill, Torben, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Gelebian, Serge, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - General Trading Co. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Gifford, James P., 1943 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Gillman, Joseph, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Globus, J.H., 1940 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Glomset, Daniel J., 1942 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Galati, Charles, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Galdston, Iago, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Garbat, A.L., 1935 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Garber, James R., 1930 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Garrison, F.H., 1931 1934 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Gates, Frederick L., 1929 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Gay, F.P. [re], 1934 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - General Accident Fire and Life Assurance Corp, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Gilbert and Association, American Association, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Gilchrist, A. Rae, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Gilson, Julius P., 1928 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Gladstone, Sidney A., 1935 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Glaser, Otto, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Globus, J.H. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Glueck, Bernard, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Gasser, Herbert S., 1940-1946 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Gasser, Herbert S., 1946-1953 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Gerontological Society, 1948-1949 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Giroux, Robert, 1947-1948 1952 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Glazer, Israel, 1947-1948 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Garrey, W.E., 1923 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Gee, Henrietta, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Geographical Society, American, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Gilchrist, A. Rae, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Godsick, William H., 1926 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Goldschmidt, Reid, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Goldschmidt, Katherine, 1924, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Goldsmith, Harry B. and Alice, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Goldsmith, James A., 1924 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Goldwater, S.S., 1924 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Gray; Horace, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Greene, Roger, 1924-1927 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Gregg, Alan, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Gruenberg, Benjamin C., 1927 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Guilfoy, William H., 1926 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Gwyn, Norman B., 1927 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Goebel, Walther F. and Mrs., 1952-1953 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Goetz, Norman S., 1948 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Gold, Harry, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Goldman, Betty, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Goldschmid, Edna, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Goldwater, Clara A., 1947 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Goodman, Joseph I., 1946 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Goodner, Kenneth, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Graef, Irving, 1948-1949 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Graham, Philip, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Grant, R.T., 1946 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Gregg, Donald E., 1947 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Greif, Carol, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Grinker, Ray R., 1946 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Grunbaum, Adolf, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Guerard, Albert, 1934 1951 1953 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Guinzburg, Harold, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Gumpert, Martin, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Göfttingen celebration, 1937 1940 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Gold, Harry, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Goldfarb, A.J. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Goldwater, S.S., 1930-1931 1935 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Goldsmith, Margery, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Golub, J.J., 1929-1930 1935 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Gonzalez, Dr., 1929 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Gordon, Samuel M., 1933 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Graef, Irving, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Gray, John W., 1935 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Green, Robert G., 1930 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Greenebaum, Mrs. F.H., 1933 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Greenwald, Amelia, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Greenway, James C., 1931-1931 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Gregg, Alan, 1932 1934 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Groedel, Franz M., 1932-1935 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Grollman, Arthur, 1931-1934 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Gross, Edward J., 1928 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Gross, Louis, 1931-1933 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Grünbaum, Franz (of Bad Nauheim), 1930 1933-1934 1937 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Grünbaum, Franz (of Berlin), 1938 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Gruenberg, Benjamin C., 1934 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Goldwater, S.S.x (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Goodner, Kenneth, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Goodwin, W.A.R., 1939 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Graef, Irving, 1937-1938 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Grant, John, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Grant, R.T., 1936 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Gray, Irving, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Graybiel, Ashton, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Greenberg, R., 1937 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Greene, Roger (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Gregg, Alan (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Gregg, Alan, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Griffiths, Charles M. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Guinzburg, Harry (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Goebel, Walther F. and Mrs., 1940-1942 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Goldblatt, Harry, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Goldfarb, A.J., 1942-1943 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Goldman, Hetty, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Goldwater, Laura, 1943-1944 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Goldwater, S.S., 1942 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Goldwater, S.S. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Gomez, Domingo M. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Goodner, Kenneth, 1943, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Goodridge, M. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Graef, Irving, 1942-1944 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Green, M. Brenn, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Grinnell, Leslie, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Groedel, Franz M., 1940 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Gross, Desiderio, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Grover, Allen, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Grunsfeld, Mary Jane (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Grundfest, Harry, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Guile, Herbert V., 1943 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Goldfeder, Anna, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Gregg, Alan, 1940-1945 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Greene, Roger, 1940-1945 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Gutwillig, George, 1930 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Guggenheim Fellowships, 1940-1944 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Halsey, J.T., 1925 1929 1931 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Halsey, J.T. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Halsey, R.H. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Halsey, R.H., 1928-1929 1932 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Hamburger, Walter W., 1929 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Hammond, Percy, 1931 1933 1935 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Haagensen, Cushman D, 1947 1949 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Hammerstein, Oscar II, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Hampshire Gazette, Daily, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Hand, Frances, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Hand, Learned, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Hadassah, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Halle, Julia, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Halperin, Stanley, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Halsey, J.T., 1943-1945 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Halsey, R.H., 1943-1944 1948 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Hand, Learned, 1942-1943 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Hanson, Rose, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Hackett, Mrs., 1936 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Hadassah Hospitals, 1923-1926 (Box 12, Folder 6-7)
  - Hackett, Francis and Toksvig, Signe, 1940-1943 1945 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Herdman, Ramona, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Hare, Michael M., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Harris, Richmond J., 1942 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Harrison, Ross G., 1940 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Harrower, Molly, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Hartung, Edward F., 1940-1944 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Hastings, A. Baird, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Hauptman, Alfred, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Hawley, Paul R. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Halsey, Robert H. ca, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Harned, F.P., 1924 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Harris, Benedict R., 1926-1927 1929 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Harris, Louis I., 1926 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Hart, Joseph K., 1926 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Harper, F.A., 1947 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Harvey Society, 1930-1931 1936 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Harris, Martin [re], 1937 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Harand, Mrs. Irene (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Harcourt, Brace, and Co., 1939 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Harrison, Tinsley (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Harrop, George A., 1936-1937 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Hart, T. Stuart (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Hastings, A. Baird, 1936 1938 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Hayme, Don, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Hart, T. Stuart, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Harvey, Samuel C., 1928 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Hyman, Harold Thomas, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Hardy, Lady, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Harris, Benedict R., 1928-1929 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Harrison, T.R. (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Hartwell, John A, 1928-1929 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Haskell, Charles C., 1935 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Hastings, A. Baird, 1928 1930 1932-1933 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Heard, James C., 1928 1933-1934 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Hektoen, Ludvig, 1928-1932 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Hentel, Celia, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Herrick, James B., 1930 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Herringham, Wilmot P., 1934 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Hertz, John Jr. [re] (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Hertzberger, Menno, 1928 1930 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Hess, Alfred F. and Sara, 1928-1935 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Heuer, George, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Heuer, George (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Heymans, C., 1929 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Highman, Walter James, 1929 1932 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Hill, N. Gray, 1929-1930 1932 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Hiller, Friedrich, 1929 1933 1935 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Hindle, Charles F., 1930 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Hirsch, Walter A. Mrs., 1929 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - History of Medicine, International Congresses, 1930 1935 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Heard, James C. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Henderson, L.J., 1926 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Heron, E.W., 1923 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Herrick, W.W., 1927 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Hill, A.V., 1925-1926 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Hill, C.L., 1924 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Hiller, Friedrich, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Hixon, Alfred J., 1923 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Hecht, Selig and Celia, 1947-1948 1951 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Herson, Charles J., 1947 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Higginson, Sally, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Hill, C.L., 1947 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Hirchberg, Alexandre, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Hindle, Charles (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Hiss, Alger, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Health Department, New York City (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Heard, James, 1938 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Hecht, Selig (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Hecht, Selig, 1938-1939 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Hedley, O.F., 1936-1939 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Hefter, Tella [re] (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Herald Tribune, New York, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Hermens, F.A., 1936-1939 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Hess, Sara, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Hiller, Friedrich, 1936 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Himwich, H.E., 1936 1939 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Hirsch, I. Seth, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - History of Science Society, 1936-1939 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Heard, James D., 1942-1944 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Hebrew University, American Friends of, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Hecht, Maressa, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Hecht, Selig, 1944-1945 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Heikes, Helen E. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Heimann, Edward, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Hektoen, Ludvig, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Heller, Harry S. [re], 1944 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Herman, Mrs. William (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Hermens, F.A., 1940-1941 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Hermens, F.A. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Hess, Sara S., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Hicks, Hamilton, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Hiller, Frederick, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Hinton, W.H., 1942-1945 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Hiss, Alger [re], 1950 1952-1953 (Box 13, Folder 7-14)
  - History of Medicine, American Association of, 1948 1951 1955 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - History of Science Society, 1946-1947 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Herald Tribune, New York, 1944-1945 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Hebrew University, 1928 1930-1931 1933-1934 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Hoagland, Charles L., 1940-1941 1945 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Hodges, Fred J., 1944-1945 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Hoerlin, Herman and Mrs., 1942 1944 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Hoffman, Edna N., 1940 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Hoffman, Ruth, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Hofstatter, Leopold (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Holland, E.O., 1941-1945 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Hooker, D.R., 1941-1942 1944 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Hooker, H.L., 1945 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Hopkins, Harry L., 1940 1941 1943 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Horsfall, Frank L., 1944-1945 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Houda, Emilian O., 1944 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Howard, John B., 1942 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Howard, Roy, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Howbert, Mary, 1940-1941 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Howe, Quincy, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Howell, William [re], 1945 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Hochhauser, Edward, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Hoenix, J.N.M., 1945 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Hoffman, Isidor B., 1944 1951 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Holland, E.O., 1946 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Holland, Kenneth, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Hooker, H.L., 1947 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Horsfall, Frank L. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Horsfall, Frank L., 1947-1950 1953 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Hovde, Bryn J., 1949 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Howbert, Irving Mrs., 1946 1953 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Holman, Delavan V. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Holman, Delavan V., 1939-1943 1945 1947 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Home for Aged and Infirm Hebrews, 1936-1939 1941 1946 (Box 14, Folder 3-11)
  - Hoagland, Charles L., 1939 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Hober, Rudolf (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Hoeber, Paul B. Inc., 1937 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Hoffman, Willia, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Holman, Delavan V., 1936-1939 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Hooker, D.R., 1936-1938 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Hooker, H.L., 1938 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Horkheimer, Max, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Horsfall, Frank L., 1936 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Howell, A.C. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Howell, J. Georgena, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - History of Science Society, 1924-1926 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Hoeber, Paul B. Inc., 1923 1926 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Hoist, Peter F., 1924 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Houghton, Henry S., 1924-1926 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Howard, Harvey J., 1926 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Howell, W.H., 1926 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Holman, Delavan V., 1946-1948 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Huang, C.H., 1941 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Huebsch, B.W. (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Huebsch, B.W., 1940-1942 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Humphreys, George H., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Humphreys, George H. II, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Humphreys, G.H. II (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Hu Shin, 1940 1942 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Hutchins, Robert M. (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Hutchins, Robert M., 1944 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Hyara, Leslie (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Hyam, Leslie, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Hyara, Harold Thomas, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Hyman, J.C. (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - History of Science Society, 1928-1932 1934 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Hochrein, Max, 1929-1932 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Hodges, Paul C., 1930 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Hoeber, Paul B. Inc., 1928-1931 1933 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Hoffman, Frederick L., 1929 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Holman, Delavan V., 1934 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Holmes, George W., 1929 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Holtz, Edward, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Hooker, D.R., 1932 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Hooper, Franklin H., 1929 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Hopkinson, Mrs. [re], 1933 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Hospital Social Service Magazine, 1932-1933 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Hospital, Saint Francis, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Howard, CP., 1930 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Howard, Tasker, 1929 1933 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Howe, F. Stanley, 1930 1935 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Hume, Edgar E., 1935 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Hussey, Raymond, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Hutchins, Robert F. (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Hutchins, Robert F., 1930 1932-1933 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Hyman, Harold, 1928-1929 1931-1934 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Holman, Delavan V., 1937, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Hu Shih, 1936 1938-1939 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Hubbart, Edith, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Hunter, W.S., 1937 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Hurd, Laura B., 1936 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Hyam, Katherine E., 1937 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Hutchins, Robert M., 1938-1940 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Huber, Freda, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Hyam, Katherine E., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Hudson, H.L., 1949 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Hyman, Harold, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Hyman, Joseph C., 1946 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Hu Shih, 1927 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Hyman, Sol, 1926-1927 (Box 15)
  - Irvington House, 1920-1921 1926 1928 1931-1932 1934 undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Iglesias, Manuel de la Pila, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - International Student Service (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Irwin, Florence, 1935-1936 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Ivins, William, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Ivins, Barbara, 1938-1939 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Ickes, Harold L., 1949 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Ingvolstad, Mrs. K, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Ireland, Bernard P., 1947 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Ireland, R.M., 1949 1953 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Ives, Kenneth and Co., 1947 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Ivins, William, 1947-1949 1951-1954 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - International Medical Relations, Committee on, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Ikle, Charles, 1934 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Immaculata, Sister, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Ingham, James, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - International Hygiene Exhibition, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - International Mercantile Marine Co., 1929 1933 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Ivins, William, 1929-1930 1932 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Ivins, Florence, 1928 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Ivins, Barbara, 1933-1934 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Ingersoll, Ralph, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - International News Service, 1945 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Isaacs, Stanley, 1941-1942 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Ivins, William, 1940 1943 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Ivins, Barbara, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Inada, Ryokichi, 1924, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Investigation., American Society for Clinical, 1936-1938 1946-1956 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Investigation, Journal of Clinical, 1935-1938 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Jacobi, S.Y., 1929 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Jacobs, M.H., 1931 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Jacobs, Walter A., 1928 1931-1933 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Jacobson, Edmund, 1930-1931 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Jacobson, Murray B., 1934 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - James, Henry, 1930-1931 1933 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - James, Mrs. Bayard, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Janowsky, Oscar I., 1933-1935 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Jarisch, A., 1929 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Jenks, Prof., 1928 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Jennings, Prof. H.S. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Jewish Statistical Bureau (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Jewish Telegraphic Agency, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Jobling, James W., 1931 1933-1934 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Johnson, Alvin, 1930 1934 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, American, 1928 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Jones, Mr. and Mrs., 1934 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Jones, Benjamin F., 1930 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Jones, F.S., 1933 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Josephi, Marion, 1933 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Journal of Philosophy, 1928 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Judson, De Witt C., 1934 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Jull, M.A., 1928 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Jung, C.G., 1930 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Juster, Irving R., 1932 1935 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Hopkins, Harry, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Jackson, Bill, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Jackson, Robert H., 1944-1945 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Jacobs, Walter A., 1940 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Jager, E. Marion, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - James, Henry, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - "Janus", 1941 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Johnson, Emily W, 1945 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Johnson, Alvin (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Jolliffe, Norman, 1941 1943 1945 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Jones, T. Duckett, 1945 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Joslin, Elliott P., 1945 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Juster, Irving R., 1940-1943 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Jackson, R.L., 1939 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Jacobs, Walter J., 1936 1938 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Jacobson, Edmund, 1937 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Jacobsohn, Dr. Leo (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - James, Henry, 1936 1938 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Janowsky, Oscar I., 1939 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Jarrett, Miss (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Jarrett, Mary C., 1939 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Jean, F.C., 1936 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Jedel, Celeste, 1936 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Jennings, H.S. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Jessup, Philip, 1936 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Jobling, James W., 1937 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Johnson, Alvin (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Jones, Polly, 1937 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Juster, Irving, 1936-1938 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Joint Distribution Dommittee, American, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Jackson, Robert H., 1946 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Jackson, William Harding, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - James, Mrs. MacGill, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Jenkins, Charles E.S., 1947 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Johnson, Alvin, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Jones, A. Morgan, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Joseph, Samuel, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Joslin, Elliott P., 1949 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Jacobs, Walter A., 1926, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Jacobs, Laura D., 1926 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - James, Henry, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Jamieson, Ross A., 1926, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Johnson, Alvin, 1927 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Jelliffe, Smith Ely, 1930-1935 (Box 16, Folder 4-7)
  - Journal Club, 1937-1954, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Kaempfer, Dr. and Mrs. Louis G., 1926 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Kaiser, Albert D., 1924 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Katz, Louis N., 1927 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Katzenstein, Arthur, 1924 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Kanf, Emil, 1924 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Kellogg, Paul H., 1927 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Kennedy, May L., 1923 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Knight, Augustus S., 1923 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Kaempffert, Waldemar, 1936-1938 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Karelson, Frank D. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Kast, L. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Kaufman, M. Ralph (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Kellogg, Paul (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Kelson, Saul R., 1937 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Kennedy, Foster, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Koehler, Mrs. Phyllis B. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Katz, Louis N., 1936 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Keck, E.H., 1936 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Kees, Walter T., 1938 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Keppel, F.B., 1939 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Kerr, Wm. J., 1939 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Kaempffert, Waldemar (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Kagan, Solomon R., 1934 (Box 17, Folder 1)